

I have been designing, building, and launching meaningful products for over a decade. During that time, I've developed broad, yet very deep, skillsets from **design** to **code**, **data analysis** to **strategy**, **branding** to **marketing**, and more.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Director of Product • Stem Disintermedia • 2019 - Present

- Established and implemented product development practices across product, design, and engineering functions.
- Own and develop the overall product roadmap in conjunction with key stakeholders and key functions across the organization.
- Owned, executed, and launched all components for Stem's advances product Scale.
- Owned, executed, and launched all components for Stem's latest offering Recoup.

VP of Product • Gallant • 2019

- As a founding member of Gallant, I worked directly with the CEO to develop the Gallant product from scratch.
- Owned and executed all areas necessary to bring our product to market: Discovery, branding, willingness to pay, product-market fit, pricing strategy, product offering, operations, logistics, industrial design, digital infrastructure, and more.

Director of Product • Ritual • 2017 - 2019

- Established process and practice for managing a product roadmap that served the needs of both Ritual's customers and the needs of Ritual's internal teams including Marketing, Operations, Creative, and Customer Service.
- Hired and built a product team from zero to a team of over 10.
- Lead the build-out of product, design, engineering, and data departments along with their cross-functional practices and workflows.
- Lead all efforts for a major re-platform from Shopify to a an in-house custom application to facilitate business goals and customer needs.

Director of Product • DogVacay • 2016 - 2017

- Owned communication of our acquisition to the DogVacay sitter community.
- Worked directly with data and analytics to define leading indicator metrics of sitter onboarding success.
- Defined retention metrics for both supply and demand side of the marketplace and leveraged those metrics into re-building DogVacay's search algorithm from scratch.

Sr. Product Manager • DogVacay • 2015 - 2016

- Defined retention metrics for both supply and demand side of the marketplace and leveraged those metrics into re-building DogVacay's search algorithm from scratch.
- Ran dozens of Optimizely A/B experiments writing front-end code for removing customer barriers, search filter prominence, and meaningful messaging.

Product Manager • DogVacay • 2014 - 2015

- Re-wrote all customer-facing email templates (both transactional and marketing) in line with growth initiatives and aligned to new company branding.
- Built iOS and Android app store presence and App Store Optimization via App Annie insights, best practices, and regular release cycle cadence.

Mobile Product Manager • Internet Brands • 2011 - 2014

- Identified and executed major opportunities in the mobile space by analyzing mobile site traffic trends across the entire Internet Brands portfolio.
- Leveraged my mobile app expertise to maintain a white-label app build pipeline for the vBulletin suite of products.

Project Manager • W2MD • 2010 - 2011

• Launched over a dozen iOS apps wearing all the hats of app designer, project manager, marketer, and app landing page builder.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts • Berklee College of Music, 2010

Major in Music Production and Engineering. Guitar as Principal Instrument.

Master Certificate • Berklee Music Online, 2007

Music Technology and Production.

VOLUNTEER WORK

Camp Director • YMCA Camp Round Meadow • 2012 - Present

I am a camp director overseeing all aspects of a week-long summer camp for children consisting of 50 total staff and 150 campers.

Youth Advisor • California Youth & Government • 2012 - 2014

California Youth & Government is a mock legislature and court system for high-school kids to participate in a hands-on democratic process. I was an advisor over the course of the public school year including 2 training conferences at Camp Roberts and the Model Legislature and Court conference in Sacramento, California.

Camp Counselor • YMCA Camp Round Meadow • 2006 - 2012

Serving as a camp counselor for a week-long summer camp in Big Bear, California. Teaching and mentoring kids ages 7 - 13 while having a great time connecting with nature and participating in camp activities.